DAVID ISRAEL LEDEZMA GURROLA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

WORK EXPERIENCE



Frontend developer

Grupo Salinas

Julio 2022 - Febrero 2023

- Platform management and administration VTEX (e-commerce)
- Creation, optimization, and maintenance of platform modules VTFX
- Creation, optimization, and maintenance of modules React
- Consumption and creation of functions API Rest with Express is and GraphQL
- Performance of functional and unit tests for product quality
- Use of agile methodologies SCRUM (certification) and AGILE
- Sonarqube optimizations



Full stack developer

Dynamic solutions

Abril 2019 - Julio 2022

- Creation, optimization, and maintenance of modules React
- Consumption and creation of functions API Rest with Express.js and GraphQL
- Creation, optimization, and maintenance of modules React Native
- Requirements analysis
- Creation and maintenance of Landing pages with React and Wordpress
- Google Cloud Platform Management



Freelancer

Febrero 2019 - Mayo 2022

- Creation of a web system for registering people to a political party based on React.js
- Creation of API Rest with Express.is
- · Creation and design of SQL database



Tecnico especialista

CIS International

Agosto 2018 - Febrero 2019

- Urban Security Project (C5) by the Jalisco state government
- Installation route planning
- Assembling and programming of switches and boards
- Security camera setup

SUMMARY

Full stack with more than 4 years of experience in development with knowledge of modern technologies.

Creation and administration of web, mobile, and E-commerce systems of different types.

Passionate about technology, movies, and learning new things.

SKILLS

- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React.js / React native
- Vtex
- Node
- GraphQL
- API REST
- SQL / NoSQL
- · Agile methodologies
- Git

CONTACT

- in linkedin.com/in/israel-ledezma
- israeledezmag@gmail.com
- 33 34424120
- Portafolio

ACADEMIC TRAINING



Computer science engineering

Universidad de Guadalajara

Centro Universitario de Tonala

2016 - 2019